Join CTO Moataz Soliman as he explores the potential impact poor performance can have on your bottom line. 👉 [Register Today](https://www.instabug.com/events/the-revenue-impact-of-mobile-app-quality-webinar)

[UPDATES

Perfect your app’s user experience with Instabug’s Flows, Feature Flags, AI visual insights and much more this Summer!](https://instabug.com/launch)

Product

[

Product Overview

The all-in-one solution for proactive and reactive feedback](https://instabug.com/product)

Test Your App Before Every Release

[

Bug Reporting

Receive reports from users with the context needed to fix issues](https://instabug.com/product/bug-reporting)[

Crash Reporting

Identify crash frequency and severity with comprehensive logs](https://instabug.com/product/crash-reporting)[

App Performance Monitoring

Align teams around one quality metric to decide whether to build or fix](https://instabug.com/product/app-performance-monitoring)

Improve Your App Stability

[

Session Replay

See exactly what your users are experiencing in real-time](https://instabug.com/product/session-replay)[

Flows

NEW

Optimize your critical user journeys and reduce drop-offs](https://instabug.com/product/flows)[

App Ratings and Reviews

Debug and monitor app ratings and reviews](https://instabug.com/product/app-ratings-reviews)

Collect Actionable User Feedback

[

Release Management

Take full control of your mobile app's phased rollout](https://instabug.com/product/release-management)[

Feature Flags

NEW

Track feature flag performance to find and mitigate issues](https://instabug.com/product/feature-flags)[

In-App Surveys

Receive reports from users with the context needed to fix issues](https://instabug.com/product/in-app-surveys)

Platform

[Why Instabug

Unlock mobile app-specific insights to fix and fend off mobile meltdowns](https://instabug.com/platform/why-instabug)

[

Automated Reproduction

Reproduce crashes and bugs without the need to maintain breadcrumbs](https://instabug.com/platform/automated-reproduction)[

Team Performance

Foster a performance culture and establish scalable workflows and processes](https://instabug.com/platform/team-performance)

[

User-Centric Insights

Get a clear picture of what your users experience to prioritize and fix issues](https://instabug.com/platform/user-centric-insights)[

Release Centered

Track and organize release-specific metrics to improve performance](https://instabug.com/platform/release-centered)

Developers

[

Docs](https://docs.instabug.com/)[

Help Center](https://help.instabug.com/en/?utm_source=website-hc&utm_medium=hc&utm_campaign=header-hc&utm_content=v1)

platforms

[

iOS](https://instabug.com/platforms/ios)[

Android](https://instabug.com/platforms/android)[

Flutter](https://instabug.com/platforms/flutter)[

Cordova](https://instabug.com/platforms/cordova)[

React Native](https://instabug.com/platforms/react-native)[

Xamarin](https://instabug.com/platforms/xamarin)

Integrations

[

Jira](https://instabug.com/integrations/jira)[

Github](https://instabug.com/integrations/github)[

Datadog](https://instabug.com/integrations/datadog)[

Slack](https://instabug.com/integrations/slack)[

Zapier](https://instabug.com/integrations/zapier)[

Okta](https://instabug.com/integrations/okta)

Resources

Tools

[Sentiment Analysis

Reproduce crashes and bugs without the need to maintain breadcrumbs](https://instabug.com/sentiment-analysis)[ROI Calculator

Get a clear picture of what your users experience to prioritize and fix issues](https://instabug.com/roi-calculator)

[Featured

Benchmark Report

Mobile App Stability Outlook 2023

Get a holistic view of the current state of mobile app stability

Read More

](https://instabug.com/mobile-app-stability-outlook-2023)

Product

Platform

Developers

Platforms

Integrations

Resources

Tools

Privacy Policy
==============

Updated: June 6th, 2023

Instabug, Inc. ("Instabug", “we”, “us”, and/or “our”) knows that you care about how your personal data is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our treatment of your personal data.

### Introduction

By using the www.instabug.com website (“**Site**”) and any related services and/or features (together with the Site, the "**Service**") you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your data, please contact us at privacy@instabug.com

### Scope

This Privacy Policy covers Instabug's treatment of personal data ("Personal Data") that Instabug gathers when you access or otherwise use the Service. It explains what data we collect, why we collect the data, how it is used and your rights and choices. While providing our Service, we may collect information about our customers’ end-users at the direction of and on behalf of our customers. Our use of this information is governed by our agreement with the applicable customer and the customer’s privacy policies. We do not control and are not responsible for the privacy policies or privacy practices of our customers or any other third parties. We encourage you to review any such policies or practices that apply to you carefully.

### 1- What Personal Data does Instabug collect?

**Information That You Provide To Us.** Instabug collects the information you voluntarily submit to the Service as follows:

* **Account Creation** - We may collect information when you create your account, including your name, email address, mailing address and phone number,
* **Payment Information** - We may collect information and details associated with your purchases, including payment-related information collected by our third-party payment processors on our behalf. We do not directly collect or store any payment card information, but may receive billing address or other non-sensitive information associated with your payment card from our third-party processors.
* **Your Communications With Us** - We collect Personal Data that is entered on our Site or is sent to us electronically when you request customer or technical support, request a product demo, register for a webinar or other event, complete any “free text” boxes in our forms (for example, support request or survey submission), apply for a job, or otherwise communicate with us.
* **User-Generated Content** - We may collect Personal Data voluntarily disclosed by you on our forums, blogs and our other areas of the Service to which you can post information and materials.

**Information Received From Third-Party Services.** If you connect to the Service using credentials from a third-party service or sign-in services such as OAuth (for example, login with a GitHub or Google account), these services will authenticate a user’s identity and provide the user with the option to share certain Personal Data, such as name and email address(es), with us.

**Automatically Collected Data.** Whenever you interact with the Service, we automatically receive and store certain types of information including information that your browser automatically sends. Such information may include your IP address (which is briefly collected to identify the country you are connecting from at the time you visit the Site, after which the IP address is deleted), domain server, and type of Internet browser.

In addition, we may collect service-related, diagnostic, and performance information. This includes high level information about your activity (such as diagnostic, crash, and performance logs and reports).

We may also collect general device information when you access or use the Service. This may include your operating system, device connectivity, and other general diagnostic data. We do not collect device IDs or other specific device identification data.

**Cookies and Similar Technologies.** Like many online services, we may use tracking technologies, such as cookies and similar technologies (e.g. web beacons and pixels) in order to automatically collect and store this information. Specifically, we may use the following technologies:

* **Cookies**, which are text files that websites store on a visitor’s device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser for the purpose of helping you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, enabling functionality, helping us understand user activity and patterns, and facilitating analytics and online advertising.
* **Local storage technologies**, like HTML5 and Flash, that provide cookie-equivalent functionality but can store larger amounts of data, including on your device outside of your browser in connection with specific applications.
* **Web beacons**, also known as pixel tags or clear GIFs, which are used to demonstrate that a webpage or email address was accessed or opened, or that certain content was viewed or clicked.

**How does Instabug use cookies?**

Instabug uses different categories of cookies to provide, protect, improve, and promote our website and services. Instabug only retains personal data for as long as is needed for the purposes for which it was collected. Information on these categories and their purposes are described below.

**Strictly necessary cookies**

These are cookies that are essential in order to operate the website and services.

**Category**

**Purpose**

**Data elements**

**Expiration**

**Third parties**

Strictly necessary

Cookies that are used to operate the website and services, such as to log you in and keep your account secure.

Categories of data collected for these purposes include authentication data, unique ID, browser information, and language settings.

These cookies are set to expire after times ranging from 30 days to 4 years.

‍

**Non-essential cookies**

These are all other cookies that are not considered strictly necessary but are used for a number of purposes when you interact with our website and services. These purposes include:

**Category**

**Purpose**

**Data elements**

**Expiration**

**Third parties**

Analytics

Cookies that help us and our partners understand how our websites are engaged with, such as usage statistics or to reconstruct viewed UI elements, in order to improve and customize our services.

Categories of data collected for these purposes include website usage data, number of visits, browser and/or device information, and unique ID.

These cookies are set to expire after times ranging from session (~20 minutes) to 2 years.

Third party providers used include Google GA4, Salesforce, Clearbit, ZoomInfo, Webflow, and Segment

General marketing and advertising

Cookies that are used by Instabug and our partners to better understand the types of individuals who are interested in our products and services and how we can promote those services based on that information.

Categories of data collected for these purposes include cross website tracking data, browser information, version data, and advertisement conversion data.

These cookies are set to expire after times ranging from session (~20 minutes) to 2 years.

Third party providers used include Adobe, Marketo, Marketo Engage, and Google Ads.

Performance and functionality

Cookies which help us remember your preferences and settings in order to improve your experience when interacting with our sites and services.

Categories of data collected for these purposes include website usage data, previous help center or chat history, email address, and unique ID.

These cookies are set to expire after times ranging from session (~20 minutes) to 3 years.

Third party providers used include Heap Analytics and Calendly

Social media advertising

Cookies that are used by Instabug and our partners to understand the effectiveness of our advertisements on social media services. These cookies also help them understand your advertising preferences so they can more effectively show you our advertisements which are relevant to your interests.

Categories of data collected for these purposes include social media account details, browser and/or device data, advertisement conversion data, website usage and/or activity data, and unique ID.

These cookies are set to expire after times ranging from session (~20 minutes) to 2 years.

Third party providers used include Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn.

‍

**How can I control the data collected through cookies?**

_Browser settings:_

You can set your browser to not accept cookies, but this may limit your ability to use our services. Due to a lack of an agreed upon standard for interpreting Do Not Track (DNT) signals, our systems currently don’t respond to DNT:1 signals from browsers visiting our websites.

_Cookie preferences:_

When you use Instabug’s services, you can select which cookies you consent for Instabug to use in by clicking Cookies & CCPA Preferences in the footer of this page.

_California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA):_

You can opt out of the selling or sharing of personal information by Instabug or update your preferences, as described in the California Consumer Privacy Act, by clicking Cookies & CCPA Preferences in the footer of this page. As described below, Instabug does not sell personal information.

### 2\. How does Instabug use the information it collects?

We may use your personal information for the following purposes or as otherwise described at the time of collection:

**To Provide the Service**: We may use your information to:

* Provide, operate and improve the Service and our business;
* Enable security features of the Service, including to combat spam, malware, and other security risks;
* Communicate with you about the Service, including by responding to your requests and support inquiries, and sending announcements, updates, and security alerts; and
* Understand your needs and interests, and personalize your experience with the Service.

**Research and development**: This includes to:

* Track and analyze your interactions with the Service to better understand how to improve performance and customer experience;  
* Improve and develop new products and services; and
* Ensure quality control.

**Compliance, fraud prevention, and safety.** To protect you and the Service, we may use your information to:

* Comply with applicable laws, regulatory requirements, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities; 
* Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; 
* Enforce our [Terms of Service](https://www.instabug.com/terms); and
* Protect the safety of any person, to address fraud, security, or technical issues, or to protect the Company’s rights or property.

**Marketing**. We may use your contact details to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you, upcoming events or other promotions. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future marketing communications. Note however that as a user of our services you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Service, such as billing or service notifications. Moreover, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

Where required by applicable law (for example, if you are an individual in the EU), we will only send you marketing information by email if you consent to us doing so at the time you provide us with your Personal Data. When you provide us with your consent to be contacted for marketing purposes, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time by following the instructions to “opt-out” of receiving marketing communication in each marketing email we send you or by contacting us as indicated below.

**With your consent.** In some cases, we may specifically ask for your consent to collect, use or share your personal information, such as when required by law.

**To create anonymous, aggregated or de-identified data.** We may create anonymous, aggregated or de-identified data from your personal information and other individuals whose personal information we collect. We make personal information into anonymous, aggregated or de-identified data by removing information that makes the data identifiable to you. We may use this anonymous, aggregated or de-identified data and share it with third parties for our lawful business purposes, including to analyze and improve the Services and promote our business.

### 3\. Will Instabug share any of the personal data it receives?

Instabug only shares Personal Data with other companies or individuals outside of Instabug in the following circumstances:

\- **Feedback**: You've shared your information as a result of giving feedback within an application using the Service. We only share this information with the developer of the application, in order to assist you and the developer in communicating.

\- **Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers:** Instabug, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions: website analytics companies, providers of digital advertising services, our hosting and cloud computing service providers, providers of CRM, marketing and sales software solutions, providers of billing and processing payments functions. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific functions. Pursuant to our instructions, these parties may access, process or store Personal Data in the course of performing their duties to us and solely in order to perform the services we have hired them to provide. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

\- **Protection of Instabug and Others**: We may release Personal Data when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Instabug, our employees, our users, or others.

\- **Business Transfers**: If Instabug or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Instabug goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, Personal Data about our customers would be one of the assets that are transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any acquirer of Instabug may continue to use your Personal Data as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

\- **With Your Consent**: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Data may be shared with third parties and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information according to the applicable law.

### 4\. European Union (EU) Users

**EU Users**

The following applies if you are a user in the EU (for these purposes, reference to the EU also includes the European Economic Area countries of Iceland, Liechtenstein, and Norway).

**Data Controller**. Instabug, Inc. is the data controller for processing Personal Data provided to us through the Service. To find our registered office, please see the “Contact Us” section below.

**Your Rights**. Subject to applicable law, you have the following rights concerning your Personal Data:

**Right of access**: If you ask us, we will confirm whether we are processing your Personal Data and if so, provide you with a copy of that Personal Data along with certain other details. If you require additional copies, we may need to charge a reasonable fee.

**Right to rectification**: If your Personal Data is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to ask that we correct or complete it. If we share your Personal Data with others, we will tell them about the correction where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data so you can contact them directly.

**Right to erasure**: You may ask us to delete or remove your Personal Data, such as where you withdraw your consent. If we share your data with others, we will tell them about the erasure where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data so you can contact them directly.

**Right to restrict processing**: You may ask us to restrict or ‘block’ the processing of your Personal Data in certain circumstances, such as where you contest the accuracy of the data or object to us processing it (please read below for information on your right to object). We will tell you before we lift any restrictions on processing. If we share your Personal Data with others, we will tell them about the restriction where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data so you can contact them directly.

**Right to data portability**: You have the right to obtain your Personal Data from us that you consented to give us or that was provided to us as necessary in connection with our contract with you. We will give you your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. You may reuse it elsewhere.

**Right to object**: You may ask us at any time to stop processing your Personal Data, and we will do so:

If we are relying on a legitimate interest to process your Personal Data – unless we demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing or

If we are processing your Personal Data for direct marketing.

**Right to withdraw consent**: If we rely on your consent to process your Personal Data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal of consent will not affect any processing of your data before we received notice that you wished to withdraw consent.

**Right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority**: If you have a concern about our privacy practices, including the way we handled your Personal Data, you can report it to the data protection authority that is authorized to hear those concerns. You can find [here](https://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/items/612080) the contact details of EU data protection authorities.

**Legitimate Interest**. “Legitimate interests” means our interests in conducting our business, managing and delivering the best Service to you. This Privacy Policy describes when we process your Personal Data for our legitimate interests, what these interests are and your rights. We will not use your Personal Data for activities where the impact on you overrides our interests unless we have your consent or those activities are otherwise required or permitted to by law.

We may process or share your personal information based on the following legal basis:

* **Consent**: We may process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal information for a specific purpose.
* **Legitimate Interests**: We may process your data when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests.
* **Performance of a Contract**: Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.
* **Legal Obligations**: We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).
* **Vital Interests**: We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

Our legal bases for processing the personal information described in this Privacy Policy are described in the table below:

**Purpose of Processing**

**Legal Bases for Processing**

* To provide the Service
* To enforce our Terms of Service
* To provide Service communications
* To provide customer service
* To ensure quality control

Performance of a contract

* For research and development
* To enhance your experience
* To engage in direct marketing activities
* To facilitate business transactions

Legitimate interests

* To comply with applicable laws and regulatory requirements
* To detect and prevent illegal activities, fraud, and other prohibited activities
* To ensure network and information security

Legal obligations, public interest, or vital interests

* To enhance your experience
* To engage in third party marketing
* For any other purpose that you consent to

Consent

‍

**US Users**

If you are a resident of the United States, you may also have certain rights under the laws of your state. For example, if you are a California resident, you may have certain rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) with respect to information collected by us during the 12 months preceding your request. These include the right to (i) request access to, details regarding, and a copy of the personal information we have collected about you and/or shared with third parties; (ii) request deletion of the personal information that we have collected about you; (iii) the right to opt-out of sale of your personal information; (iv) the right to correct inaccurate personal information; and (v) the right to limit the use of your sensitive personal information. As the terms are defined under the CCPA, we do not “sell” your “personal information.”

California residents may also request the following information (to the extent we share your personal information in this way):

* the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year; and
* the names and addresses of third parties that received such information, or if the nature of their business cannot be determined from the name, then examples of the products or services marketed.

### 5\. Data Retention

We will keep your Personal Data for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, while we have a legitimate business need to do so, or as required by law (e.g. for tax, legal, accounting or other purposes), whichever is the longer.

If you have elected to receive marketing communications from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences until you opt-out of receiving these communications and in accordance with our policies.

To determine the appropriate retention period for your Personal Data, we will consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the Personal Data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your Personal Data, the purposes for which we use your Personal Data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. In some circumstances, we may anonymize your Personal Data so that it can no longer be associated with you, in which case it is no longer Personal Data.

### 6\. International Users

Instabug is based in the United States. If you are accessing our Service from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that your Personal Data will be transmitted to our servers in the United States and the data may be transmitted to our service providers supporting our business operations (described above). The United States may have data protection laws less stringent than or otherwise different from the laws in effect in the country in which you are located. Where we transfer your Personal Data out of the EU we will take steps to ensure that your Personal Data receives an adequate level of protection where it is processed and your rights continue to be protected. For information that we process on behalf of our customers, we have implemented appropriate contractual provisions (including, for data collected from the EU, the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses for data transfers) to ensure adequate protection for your Personal Data. Please contact us if you have any questions about the safeguards that we implement when we transfer your Personal Data.

### 7\. Conditions of Use

If you decide to access or use the Service, such access and use and any possible dispute over privacy are subject to this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Service](https://instabug.com/terms), including limitations on damages and disclaimer of warranties to the extent permitted by the applicable law.

### 8\. Third Party Website/Services

The Site may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Site. These other websites are not under Instabug control, and by providing these links we do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed these other websites or the services offered through them. The information that you share with such websites will be governed by the specific privacy policies and terms of service of the third-party websites and not by this Privacy Policy. Instabug is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

### 9\. Information Security

We take care to protect your Personal Data against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction, through appropriate security measures. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store Personal Data.

### 10\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

You have the following choices with respect to your Personal Data:

* **Email Communications.** If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can use the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email to opt out of receiving future marketing emails. Note that you will continue to receive transaction-related emails regarding the Service you have requested. We may also send you certain non-promotional communications regarding us and the Service, and you will not be able to opt out of those communications (e.g., updates to our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy).
* **“Do Not Track.”** Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. Please note that we do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers.
* **Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising.** You may stop or restrict the placement of Technologies on your device or remove them by adjusting your preferences as your browser or device permits. However, if you adjust your preferences, the Service may not work properly. Please note you must separately opt out in each browser and on each device.
* **Mobile Settings.** You can use your mobile device settings to limit use of the identifier(s) associated with your device for interest-based advertising purposes and for location tracking. 
* **Declining to provide information.** We need to collect personal information to provide certain services. If you do not provide the information we identify as required or mandatory, we may not be able to provide those services.

**Delete your content or close your account.** You can choose to delete certain content through your account. If you wish to request to close your account, please contact us at privacy@Instabug.com

### 11\. Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us as described below. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

You can contact us by email at [privacy@Instabug.com](mailto:privacy@Instabug.com), or our mailing address below:

Instabug, Inc.  
230 California Street  
San Francisco, CA 94111  
United States

‍

### PRODUCT

[Overview](https://instabug.com/product)[Bug Reporting](https://instabug.com/product/bug-reporting)[Crash Reporting](https://instabug.com/product/crash-reporting)[App Performance](https://instabug.com/product/app-performance-monitoring)[Session Replay](https://instabug.com/product/session-replay)[Release  
Management](https://instabug.com/product/release-management)[In-App Surveys](https://instabug.com/product/in-app-surveys)[App Ratings  
and Reviews](https://instabug.com/product/app-ratings-reviews)[Flows](https://instabug.com/product/flows)[Feature Flags](https://instabug.com/product/feature-flags)

### Integrations

### Platforms

### Comparisons

### RESOURCES

### COMPANY

[Terms and Conditions](https://instabug.com/terms) / [Website Terms of Use](https://instabug.com/website-terms-of-use) / [Privacy Policy](https://instabug.com/privacy) © 2024 Instabug, Inc.
